<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Wisecorp</title>
    <link>http://localhost:34313/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Wisecorp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:34313/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What are we looking for ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34313/about/what_are_we_looking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:34313/about/what_are_we_looking/</guid>
      <description>We are looking create a team of motivated talents, to work on our new product.
We look also to develop our consulting activity by hiring consultants, to work on our innovative projects for our international customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What did we perform yet ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34313/about/what_did/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:34313/about/what_did/</guid>
      <description>We have already developed a smart cloud-native and microservices architecture for orchestration of any application/workload over a Kubernetes platform.
Our solution, named TheCell, is capable of orchestrating on-premise and-or private/hybrid/public cloud platform, and even of mixing all of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What didn’t we perform yet ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34313/about/what_didn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:34313/about/what_didn/</guid>
      <description>We are working hard to develop our first Hardware Cell, in order to prove the validity of our Concept.
In fact, we believe that Hardware Acceleration is going Cloud-Native. So we are building a PoC where a BigData problem is handled in a HW-accelerated platform, thanks to a PaaS approach, in our Cloud-based platform.
This PoC will not only validate a huge innovation, but will also make us a pioneer and a main actor in this new Hardware-Cloud Convergence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do we do ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34313/about/what_do_we_do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:34313/about/what_do_we_do/</guid>
      <description>We are building an innovative technology that we believe to push the boundaries and simplify the use of very large Computing power, thanks to a smarter use of FPGA and to a Cloud-Native, MicroServices-based Architecture.
We also perform IT consulting for key account customers in Europe. For our team, our experts provide a very high level of training to the team, covering Cloud, Security, Networks, and DevOps technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34313/about/who_are_we/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:34313/about/who_are_we/</guid>
      <description>We are a team of technology enthousiasts, having experience in Information Technology, Electronics, Internet &amp;amp; Cloud Infrastructures, DevOps and Software Design. We have also a very strong partnership with a French security consulting company, that is already making use of our technology, and expanding its activity with us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why join us ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34313/about/why_join_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:34313/about/why_join_us/</guid>
      <description>  To evolve with a fast-growing start-up
  To make use of cutting-edge technologies, and have a high level training
  To prepare for an international carreer and a very high-demand expertise
  To grow with us : we propose stock options and managing roles for early-joiners
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
